[
    {
        "front": "かいわ",
        "back": "conversation",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "むすこ",
        "back": "son",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "（お）こ（さん）",
        "back": "child",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "いじめる",
        "back": "to bully; to be cruel to",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "かなしい",
        "back": "upset; sad",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "みえる",
        "back": "to look (sad); to be seen",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "おたく",
        "back": "you house",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "きぶん",
        "back": "feeling",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "あんしん（する）",
        "back": "relief /  to be relieved",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "つたえる",
        "back": "to communicate",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんせつな",
        "back": "kind",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "やさしい",
        "back": "good-natured; kind-hearted",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "さびしい",
        "back": "strict",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    },
    {
        "front": "しっかり",
        "back": "attentively; hard; reliable",
        "chapter": "N4 C32"
    }
]